(Yeosu)
(By day, a feast of delicious food awaits you.)
(By night, romance settles over the city.)
(We return to Yeosu, the city of romance.)
Hello, I'm...
Apparently, a lot of people like me.
Honestly, I don't know why.
(Why he came to visit the siblings)
I don't think she can live without me.
(To stir things up at the siblings')
(a catfish man has arrived.)
(What's your most attractive feature?)
I'm not sure. My charm is...
my big nose.
My nose looks like it'd bring luck.
(Shy)
I hear that quite often.
People just whisper about me...
every time I walk by. Why not just say it to my face?
My goodness.
(The owner of an irresistible charm)
Gosh, it's hot.
(Who's the dangerously charming man who can't handle the heat?)
You look like a catfish on camera.
A catfish is...
Isn't that a fish?
(The catfish man, Jeong Sang Hun)
(The Lamb Skewers and Tsingtao character on "SNL Korea")
("Mrs. Doubtfire" and "A Gentleman's Guide to Love and Murder")
(A veteran musical theater actor who's captivated audiences)
Which celebrity makes me feel threatened?
Cho Jung Seok.
(What kind of friend are you to Jung Ah?)
I'm a cutie.
Jung Ah bothers me a lot because of my charm.
(That's enough.)
I want to make unforgettable memories...
for Fresh off the Sea members.
I want to leave a mark on their lives.
(The catfish man, Jeong San Hun came...)
(to I'm a Single's Inferno at the siblings'.)
- Let me know when you're ready.
- Yes, I'm seated.
Okay.
They'll be so shocked. No one will recognise me.
(What unforgettable memory...)
(has Sang Hun prepared for the siblings?)
(A resort in Yeosu)
Gosh, my eyes.
It's so bright.
(Woman No. 1 makes her entrance.)
(Woman No. 1 ascends the stairs gracefully.)
Hello.
(Woman No. 1, Roh Yoon Seo)
(Entering with an impressively enthusiastic greeting)
How do I go in?
(Entrance)
Where is...
This way?
(A charmingly awkward woman who gets lost at the entrance)
Oh, it's this way.
Hello.
Hello. It feels very unfamiliar to be in a place like this.
(Looking around)
(Scratching)
It feels very unfamiliar.
(A suspiciously luxurious location for the opening)
(There's even an outdoor swimming pool.)
I feel like we should be filming "EXchange."
The place is so unfamiliar and way too fancy.
I bet there's ulterior motive behind this...
until the end...
It's beautiful, but I'm worried.
(As Yoon Seo grows uneasy in the luxurious place, )
(a woman appears reflected in the window.)
(Smiling)
(She might have been Miss Korea back in the day.)
Jung Ah!
You can't see anything from there.
- I can't see anything.
- Seriously.
- I couldn't see anything.
- Right?
Hi.
Hello. It's been a month.
This place is nice.
It feels unfamiliar.
- We should be filming "EXchange."
- Right.
You're supposed to ask,
"How did you get here?" Isn't that what you ask?
- How did I get here?
- How did you get here?
Is that what you ask, Jung Ah?
Isn't that what they ask on "EXchange?"
Am I wrong?
The show I watched must be...
"Better Late..."
"Than Single."
"Better Late Than Single?" Okay.
On "EXchange," it's more like...
"I saw that you went on a date with him yesterday."
"Did you have fun?"
What do they say when they meet for the first time?
When they meet for the first time?
"Hello."
Meanwhile, you scan the person from head to toe.
(Subtle flirting is essential.)
"EXchange" is the one where your exes show up.
That's right.
Gosh, the sunlight...
I should get in the shade.
Hello.
(Making her entrance as radiant as the August sunshine)
I didn't see you because of the sunlight.
(Woman No. 3, Kim Sun Young)
Hello.
Gosh, this place is so luxurious.
Look at her hands.
- Where should I sit?
- Everyone says the same thing.
My goodness.
- It's so fancy here.
- Doesn't it feel unfamiliar?
Can I get some brunch?
(It doesn't feel unfamiliar at all.)
One iced latte and a croissant, please.
(She just came to have breakfast.)
Why isn't You Seok here?
Has he not arrived yet?
At six in the morning...
- He got here at 6:30am.
- Right.
- He must be very tired.
- He probably didn't get any sleep.
(Fidgeting around)
I've dropped...
a cake before.
(Despite his busy schedule, You Seok came all the way to Yeosu.)
(He prepared a surprise for Jung Ah.)
(He's more excited than she is.)
(Quietly)
What?
(She spots You Seok.)
Is he here?
- Gosh, he brought something.
- What is it?
(Hurrying through the back door so she won't see him)
Where did he go?
I came around the other way.
Right, it's Jung Ah's birthday.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
(Happy Birthday to you)
- What happened to your arm?
- Happy Birthday to you
- What's wrong with your arm?
- All right.
Let's celebrate first.
- Happy Birthday to our dear Jung Ah - But...
Happy Birthday to you
- Let me light it.
- My goodness.
Wait, I'll light it.
- While I was...
- Did you make it?
- I didn't make it myself.
- It looks so cute.
- He's so thoughtful.
- Right.
- It looks so cute.
- I'm more worried...
about your arm than this.
During a shoot yesterday,
I slightly fractured my wrist.
It isn't a ligament injury. The doctor said that I could work.
(Worried)
Oh, no. I ruined the mood.
I'm really okay. Don't worry about me.
I'll do my best with one hand.
Right, but...
(Holding an emergency meeting about You Seok's injury)
He bumped his arm a little.
He said that it wasn't anything to worry about.
- And...
- He's injured.
We can't make him work.
(They decide to keep an eye on him through the opening shoot.)
This is our final shoot in Yeosu.
Okay.
It's sad. I had a dream about it.
A few days ago, I dreamed about our fourth shoot.
I even saw our guest.
- Who was it?
- Who was the guest?
Jae Wook came.
- Then I thought, - Lee Jae Wook?
- He's in the military.
- "He's in the military."
- When I got up in the morning, - He's in the military.
I was about to send a message to the members.
I thought, "But he's in the military."
You must have Dex and Jae Wook on your mind a lot.
Don't say that.
- Especially yesterday...
- Dex and...
- He was on a show.
- On a show yesterday...
I like you, Dex.
- Right, you like Dex.
- I really like him.
He isn't coming today, is it?
- I really miss him.
- Are you wary of him?
No, not at all.
If he comes, I won't say a word.
What is he saying?
Speaking of guests...
- Do we have a guest today?
- He's already here.
- Right here?
- Why are you telling us that?
- Here?
- Why is she telling us that?
- Where are you?
Do we have to find him?
- Why is she telling us that?
- Is he hiding?
- Right here?
- Is he wearing a hat? Hold on.
- The camera...
- What?
Isn't he wearing a hat?
Hold on. We have to look at each of them...
- He's wearing a hat.
- carefully.
Where could he be?
- There's someone suspicious.
- What's that?
- You startled me.
- Where?
- There he is.
- What?
- Gosh, what's that?
- Where?
- You startled me.
- What?
- Where?
- There he is.
(What's going on here?)
- It's a woman.
- It must be. She has long hair.
Her ankles look very thin.
(Long hair and thin ankles)
(Answer: Jeong Sang Hun with a wig)
- Our guest has arrived.
- Her ankles...
- Right.
- Have a seat first.
Please sit down. Don't go near the guest.
(Staring)
Hey, Cha Joo Young. Come out.
- Is it Cha Joo Young?
- Isn't it Cha Joo Young?
(Jeong Sang Hun)
When did you prepare all this?
- My field of vision is very narrow.
- We invited...
- a special mystery guest.
- Do we guess who it is?
If you can figure out who it is by asking ten questions,
- we'll give you a dining voucher.
- Okay.
- What?
- Really?
Seriously?
But you can only ask ten questions.
- Okay. Ten should be enough.
- Okay.
Doesn't the hair look like a wig?
How old are you?
Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
- What did he say?
- He says he's happy to meet us.
- "It's nice to meet you."
(A mysteriously distorted voice)
(Laughing)
I've been waiting for over an hour.
- What?
- He waited for over an hour.
- Really?
- Yes.
- He must be hot. I feel bad.
- You Seok.
- You Seok?
- Nice to meet you.
It must be someone who knows you.
Do you know me?
Of course. I'm your huge fan.
After watching "When Life Gives You Tangerines,"
I fell in love with you.
He refuses to answer the question.
(He talks about whatever he wants.)
How old are you?
- It sounds like...
- I am...
around the same age as Yoon Seo.
- I don't think so.
- Around the same age as Yoon Seo.
He doesn't sound like someone who's around Yoon Seo's age.
- Yes, I am.
- What?
It's a bit too much. Who is it?
- He clearly has big ambitions...
- His definition of the same age...
- in variety shows.
- It seems a bit too much.
How many of us have you worked with on a project?
- Among the four of us.
- I don't know.
- Please answer the question.
- Listen.
- Yes?
Can you please answer the question?
Why are you getting so angry?
- Is Cho Jung Seok back?
- Jung Seok...
Maybe he's someone from the production staff.
I don't know.
- What?
- He sounds older than me.
How many projects have you done with Jung Ah?
I've never worked with her.
Then he must know me personally.
Guess who I am.
(A dangerously irresistible charm that he can't hide)
- It's definitely a man.
- It's a man.
- He has broad shoulders.
And his wig looks matted down.
(Whining)
Who could it be?
- Are you an actor?
- I'm an actor.
Actor.
(Coy)
- We made him upset.
- Is there really an actor like him?
- Hurry up and ask your questions.
- An actor?
I'm dying from the heat over here.
- What?
- He asked us to hurry up.
I'm dying from the heat.
He's dying from the heat. This must be... Wait.
(She's dying laughing.)
Jung Ah, guess who it is. It's someone close to you.
His character is unbelievable.
Tell us one thing that would...
- best introduce yourself.
- That must be Sun Young.
Well, do you want to hear me sing?
- He wants to sing?
- Yes, please sing.
The applause is way too quiet.
(Welcoming him with a round of applause)
(Confidently ready to show off his singing skill)
(Singing)
What song is that?
I might recognise his voice.
(When the night)
(Has come)
(Babbling)
(What is he doing?)
- I know who it is.
- Who is it?
(Isn't it Jeong Sang Hun?)
Jeong Sang Hun.
Yes, isn't that right?
- He sings. It must be Sang Hun.
- Are you close to him?
It's Jeong Sang Hun.
It's definitely him.
When I listen to this while thinking about him...
- Should we go ahead and guess?
- Yes.
Sang Hun, you must be very hot.
What? Who?
(Sang Hun, come out now.)
Sang Hun?
What is he doing right now?
(The moment his identity is exposed...)
(He breaks into a shadow puppet show.)
(A parrot)
(Whatever)
(Thunderous applause)
What is that?
(A puppy)
(A spectacle that they've never seen before)
He's so hilarious.
(A spectacular finale)
- It must be him.
- Can I come out now?
- Yes, come out. You must be hot.
- Please say the answer.
Jeong Sang Hun.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
It's been an hour.
- I haven't waited this long.
- It's him.
(Anticipating)
(Today's guest, Jeong Sang Hun)
(Trying to play it cool)
- Seriously...
- That was amazing.
- It was so difficult.
- Wasn't it hot?
(Good to see you)
- Why are your legs...
- To be like a woman.
(Why did he tie his legs together?)
- I kept spreading my legs.
- His legs keep spreading.
That's why I tied them.
This is insane.
That's hilarious.
- Goodness.
- It was like watching a TV show.
(A celebrity among celebrities has arrived.)
- I think you two are the same age.
- Really?
- Were you born in 1976?
- In 1976.
Sun Young.
- Sang Hun.
- It's nice to meet you.
- My goodness.
- Seriously?
I didn't know.
Since you guessed correctly, here you go.
(Handing them a dining voucher for lunch)
Thank you.
Jung Ah, look. There are drawings on it.
Isn't this horse mackerel?
Won't we take a boat? We came all the way to Yeosu.
That's terrifying. Imagine how seasick we'll get.
- We had a meeting.
- Yes?
We don't think You Seok should work at all.
- So that was why.
- Even on TV...
- He's injured.
- Due to the situation,
only a few of you will go.
- You Seok will stay at home.
- Really?
- Right.
- Yes, I agree.
Making him work...
Let's check if this is actually real.
Let's check.
Let's take a look.
- Let's take a look.
- Let's check.
- My goodness.
- Gosh, be careful.
(Pulling out)
(Ta-da, I was kidding.)
He's completely fine.
- Gosh, be careful.
- Let's check.
(You Seok's candid camera prank, a fake cast)
(We know.)
But you weren't supposed to know.
Didn't you fall for it? But why did you say...
(You already knew?)
(The production staff had already caught on.)
The doctor said that my wrist was fractured.
(The suspiciously loose cast)
(His enthusiastic applause as if he forgot about his fractured hand)
(Most importantly...)
- But you're injured.
- No, it's okay.
(Acting awkward)
(Trying not to laugh)
- Were you acting too?
- Were you testing us?
But this was a little...
It was kind of sloppy.
- This looked quite sloppy.
- Right.
- It's very sloppy.
- This looked sloppy.
Actually, you sent an ambiguous text...
- on the messenger.
- About what?
I didn't know that...
- you'd show up wearing this.
- I said that I would.
(Here's the story behind the incident.)
- Gosh, what's wrong with you?
- That startled me.
(The production staff's revenge for the Taean snake incident)
(And that incident eventually led to another revenge.)
(Should I come wearing a cast the day after tomorrow?)
I thought that You Seok was only joking.
(Let's fool the production staff with a fake cast.)
- We keep disappointing you.
- You Seok.
(Laughing)
This is only the beginning.
- I want to make you happy once.
- It's only the beginning.
- I'm glad that you're not hurt.
- It's the effort that counts.
Please get changed to go to work.
- Okay.
Shall we go? Let's hit the road.
Gosh, the weather is really beautiful.
It's beautiful.
(Bright, sunny weather welcomes the siblings.)
- I'm so happy.
- Are you?
Is everyone feeling okay today? How about you, You Seok?
- He must be tired.
- Are you tired?
- Are you sleepy?
- I'm sleepy.
When did you buy...
- the flowers and cake?
- I know.
- He does a lot of preparation.
- He's very sweet.
- I can see that.
- Yes.
Once this shoot is over, I'm going to miss You Seok so much.
(You Seok is just as sad.)
You can call him and hang out.
That'd be too much effort.
Jung Ah, aren't you going to see us anymore?
- Jung Ah is...
- That's disappointing.
- How much did you sleep?
- About two hours.
You only slept two hours?
- Get some sleep now.
- You must be tired.
- He slept 1 hour in the car.
- I slept 1 hour in the car...
and one more hour after getting here.
You should get some sleep.
Get some sleep.
(Yoon Seo seems to care about You Seok more than usual.)
(Something feels different from usual.)
- We decided to start flirting.
- What?
- For the last...
- You decided to start flirting?
- So...
- You will flirt with each other?
- Yes.
They decided the concept to be dating.
- Can you really pull it off?
- She's terrible at it.
- This is what she'll do.
- Look into You Seok's eyes.
Look into You Seok's eyes.
(Bursting out laughing)
(She fails within 0.1 seconds.)
That's funny.
Imagine that you're acting.
- You're an actress.
- Okay, I'm an actress.
- In ten seconds.
- One, two, three.
- You're about to kiss.
(You Seok...)
(Longing)
- I don't laugh.
- The comedian is over there.
- Yoon Seo.
Try to concentrate. Right now, you are...
You Seok, can you lean?
Pretend like you're sleeping.
No, lean the other way.
Pretend like you're dozing off.
I'll do this.
(Screaming)
(What's going on with these two?)
(Shuddering)
(Horrified)
She must really dislike it.
It's not that...
Even before her head touched my shoulder,
- she screamed and ran away.
- Hey.
- You know what I mean?
- There's no love in his touch.
- There's no affection at all.
- I mean,
- touch her carefully.
- Right, be more careful.
Don't just drop her head on your shoulder.
- You Seok was handling her head.
- Her head.
(That's hilarious.)
From the side...
This is impossible for us.
(You don't do this with family.)
We have 17 more minutes to go.
(They're getting closer to their workplace.)
- The view is so beautiful.
- Seriously.
It feels like we're going on a trip.
I know.
(But moments later)
(Jung Ah!)
(Jung Ah collapsed.)
(The siblings collapse in the middle of labour.)
(I want to throw up.)
(They even start feeling nauseous.)
(What happened to the siblings?)
Can you sing it, Sang Hun?
(Still excited without knowing what awaits them)
This is so much fun.
I think we're here.
- It's right here.
- Here...
- This isn't the sea.
- It's not the sea.
(The road leads them to farmland.)
- I wonder what we're doing.
- What is it?
Oh, my. We arrived, and it's absolutely scorching.
- But still...
- What's this?
(Blazing sunlight without even a single cloud)
What's here anyway?
Everyone, get out.
- Let's get out immediately.
- Gosh.
The moment I stepped out, I could feel paradise and inferno.
(The heat hits them the second they step outside.)
This is incredible.
- What could possibly be here?
- Today's sun...
It's no joke.
I didn't even bring a hat.
(Literally sweltering under the sun)
- There's no cloud in sight.
- Not even a single cloud.
(The sun beats down from the cloudless sky.)
Gosh, it's hot.
- The green onions are dying.
- It's hot.
(The sunlight is so intense they can barely open their eyes.)
Come into the shade.
I hope we get to work in the shade. Right?
This is unbelievable.
(They walk along the shade to avoid the sun.)
- What?
- What is it?
(It seems like they're almost there.)
Are we picking corn? Waxy corn?
(What work will they do on such a hot day?)
(Looking around)
Chili pepper?
It's a chilli pepper field.
(Rows of chilli peppers greet them along the way to labour.)
The chilli peppers are ripe and red.
They're so beautiful.
- The spicy smell hits you.
- Is it red pepper?
- Yes.
- Red pepper.
Today's harvest will be...
Yeosu's fiery red specialty, chilli peppers.
Really?
(Today's labour, harvesting chilli peppers)
(Speaking of Anpo Village's chilli peppers)
They're surrounded by mountains...
with the sea on one side.
(Thanks to the sea breeze from the South Sea)
They grow quite well.
(Known for their vivid red colour and clean, fiery taste)
The chilli peppers are sown between April 15 and 25.
(Once the flowers fall, green chilli peppers begin to grow.)
(Leave bright green peppers hanging for more than a month, )
(and they transform into red chilli peppers.)
(All you need to do is pick them by hand with a quick snap.)
(So it looks like a simple job, )
(but there's a hidden catch.)
(As the full-blown summer heat sets in, )
(a heat wave warning was issued all over Yeosu.)
(Chili pepper harvesting in the middle of a heat wave)
It's hot.
(The camera director exhales heavily.)
I can't keep filming anymore.
(Even the staff is shocked by the heat.)
(With the low-hanging branches forcing them to work crouched down, )
(it's far more gruelling than any other farm work.)
(It's the ultimate farm work.)
(The size of today's chilli pepper field)
(It's about 661m².)
(Will the siblings make it through the chilli pepper harvest safely?)
- Gosh, hello.
- Hello.
(Helping them with today's farm work is Kim Hyo Ja.)
- When picking chilli peppers, - Right.
You don't pick the green ones.
You only pick the red ones.
These are the ones we eat fresh.
If you pick these and dry them...
- They become dried chilli peppers?
- Yes.
- They're made into chilli powder.
- Chili powder.
- You can't pick those, right?
- They have a mix of colours.
Green ones?
(Chili peppers with a mix of colours)
- Not the ones with mixed colours.
- You can't pick those.
Don't pick the green ones. Only pick the fully red ones.
(Grip the stem with both hands)
(Give it a firm tug and snap it)
You take the whole stem off?
The ripe ones are a little softer.
They're nice and smooth when you grind them.
(Once you get the hang of it, you can pick them with one hand.)
(After harvesting the chilli peppers, )
(put them into the mesh bags according to weight)
(Go ahead and pick them neatly)
The completely red ones...
Only the fully red ones.
I see.
- I got it. Thank you.
- Go ahead and pick them.
Thank you.
How much is it per mesh bag?
- Each mesh bag holds 5kg.
- Okay.
We'll pay you 20 dollars per mesh bag.
Twenty dollars per mesh bag?
(Their pay is 20 dollars per bag.)
In order to earn 100 dollars,
- we have to fill 5 bags.
- we need to fill 2 boxes, right?
Take a bucket.
- Everyone grabs a bucket.
- Yes.
Gosh, let's give it a try.
(Let's just try it.)
(Following what they've been taught, )
(they grip the stem and pull to snap the chilli pepper.)
(She masters the art of picking chilli in one go.)
(You Seok also gives it a try.)
(The chilli peppers come right off.)
(Like this)
(Carefully harvesting the peppers without damaging them)
Is the sunlight what makes them turn red?
(To help the peppers ripen into a deep red)
(There's no shade on the chilli pepper field.)
The sun is really intense.
I'm already drenched in sweat.
(Just 5 minutes into the job, their sweat glands explode.)
(Gosh, it's hot.)
You should all take a nice shower when you get home.
Of course.
Some of them don't wash themselves.
Jung Ah, what are you talking about?
We didn't take a shower only once last time.
There was a perfectly good reason.
We were going into a creek.
The water was clean.
I want to go to a creek.
On a day like today, I want to jump right in.
I want to go there too.
I want to dive right in.
(Putting their thoughts on a refreshing creek aside)
Goodness.
(They focus on the chilli pepper harvest right in front of them.)
(Gosh, it's beautiful.)
Picking chilli peppers is actually really fun.
- I like it.
- Yes.
I like it because it's simple.
There's something satisfying about the spicy smell.
- Right.
- Yes.
They're very fresh.
(Everyone is completely absorbed in picking chilli peppers.)
The chilli peppers are very plump.
- They're very big.
- Right?
Yes, they're very red too.
(Big, bright red chilli peppers that are ripe)
It's so shiny.
(Glossy)
Look, it's this big.
(Some are as big as Yoon Seo's face.)
It's as big as my palm.
The more I pick them, the more they look like fruit.
They look beautiful and appetizing.
I had no idea that chilli peppers could be this pretty.
- Right, Sun Young?
- They're so pretty.
And they're huge.
(Captivated by the charms of gorgeous chilli peppers)
They have to be bright red.
You have to pick only the fully red ones.
(Picking the reddest chilli peppers)
(The siblings give it their all.)
There are so many.
(Even when it gets tough, they keep their spirits high.)
It's nice doing this while chatting quietly.
Isn't it nice?
Sang Hun, what is it called?
Who's Sang Hun?
- Isn't he Sang Hun?
- Who?
- I'm Ssang Soon.
- Ssang Soon.
And I like chilli peppers.
What are you saying exactly?
- What are you saying?
- Here we go again.
- Gosh, that's embarrassing.
- There he goes again.
It's small but spicy.
Goodness, I don't know.
(The atmosphere starts heating up.)
This chilli pepper field is definitely spicy.
- It's spicy.
- It's definitely spicy.
Chili peppers arrived in Korea...
much later than the Joseon dynasty.
- Really?
- It was a foreign crop.
Is that so?
(The Useless but Interesting Encyclopedia of Chili Peppers)
So we didn't originally have chilli powder?
Exactly. We used to only make white kimchi.
Apparently, we only had white kimchi in the past.
Is that true? My goodness.
(A theory that chilli peppers were introduced to Korea through Japan)
- I had no idea.
- That's right.
My goodness.
Who brought this red vegetable to Korea?
Was it Mun Ik Chom?
(I'm not sure about that part.)
(Laughing)
(Mun Ik Chom brought cotton seeds.)
(That's hilarious.)
- Gosh.
- "Was it Mun Ik Chom?"
(He must've been busy bringing cotton seeds and chilli peppers.)
Goodness.
He said that it was Mun Ik Chom.
(His knowledge is wide yet shallow.)
(20 minutes into their labour work)
(Groaning)
(Exclaiming)
Gosh, it's burning hot.
(With time, the heat gets increasingly intense.)
It's really hot.
I can really feel the heat now that I'm working.
The ones buried deep inside are so hard to pick.
- You can't reach them, right?
- Right.
They're so tangled up.
(Red chilli peppers are hiding deep inside the tangled branches.)
They're all hiding.
If they were hanging outside, I'd pick them much faster.
It'd be easier if you could see them easily.
- They're hiding.
- I have to reach my hand...
- far inside. This is hard.
- It's hard.
I can't speed up.
Are they here?
(Red chilli peppers, where are you hiding?)
(On the other hand, )
(You Seok is good at picking only the red chilli peppers.)
(Every single one he picks is a bright red chilli pepper.)
I have a chilli pepper field back home.
(It turns out that he's the chilli pepper prince.)
But you've never done this before, right?
Of course not.
I thought that it was easy, so I never helped out.
- Because you thought it was easy?
- That's why you didn't help out?
Because it's easy.
Mother and Father.
Your bad son is crying.
He should've helped out knowing that it was hard work.
(The chilli pepper prince picks chilli peppers...)
(as if seeking redemption.)
(Working hard)
(You Seok's basket is filling up with red chilli peppers.)
(He's still harvesting nonstop.)
You Seok, look at her. Look how fast she is.
(Threatening the chilli pepper prince)
Gosh, we're good at this work.
(Picking 2 while others pick only 1)
(The difference in speed is clear.)
I'll work even faster.
(The chilli peppers are piling up at an incredible speed.)
Watching this show yesterday, I realised...
how great Yoon Seo is at work.
When she was harvesting sea squirt...
- and...
- This is no big deal.
- She's smart.
- Also when she dug garlic.
(Once she clears them out hiding inside the branches)
I'm done.
She's really good.
(She's the first one to fill the entire bucket.)
I'll dump them inside the basket for now.
(They'll put them in mesh bags later and weigh them.)
Yes, we'll take care of them later.
(Yoon Seo did a good job picking only the red, ripe peppers.)
I'm confident when it comes to using my hands.
She studied art.
- Is that so?
- She studied art.
I also...
used to draw back in the day.
- Ssang Soon, did you draw too?
- That's right.
I'm good at drawing.
So you have amazing hand skills.
(Picking out only the bright red chilli peppers)
Gosh, I filled up one bucket already.
(Being an art major gives you some impressive hand skills.)
(I'd better hurry up too.)
(When you snap and pick each chilli pepper)
(Before you know it, everyone has filled their bucket.)
Everyone is working so fast.
The colour is really beautiful.
(Within 30 minutes, they fill up one yellow basket.)
Now that I'm standing up,
the field we have to harvest is no joke.
(It's huge.)
- It won't be easy.
- Right. We have to pick them fast.
(They work with both hands as fast as possible.)
Gosh, it's hot.
(Exhaling)
(Panting)
(The heat is closing in on them more and more.)
Gosh, it's hard.
(The current temperature at the chilli pepper field)
The weather is insane.
When you stand up, there's a bit of breeze.
Goodness, I wish they wouldn't be hiding.
There's no wind. The heat is radiating from the ground.
- Doesn't it feel like 40°C today?
- It's hotter.
(It's 1 of the hottest days ever on Fresh off the Sea 3.)
(Their faces are turning bright red.)
Gosh, this is exhausting.
My sweat is pouring down.
(Beads of sweat)
I'm drenched in sweat.
(Wiping away the running sweat)
Goodness.
(His sweat keeps dripping, and he can't do anything about it.)
(Under the blazing sun)
I'm sweating on my back.
(The siblings are getting exhausted at an alarming rate.)
I'm dizzy. I feel like throwing up.
(The sight of me crying)
(I look so pathetic)
(I hate this)
(Bright, blazing sun)
(Gasping)
(Exclaiming)
(It's insanely hot.)
I'm sweating...
like crazy.
(Is it sweat or tears?)
I'm about to collapse.
(Very close to collapsing)
Can I get a sip of cold water?
(After rehydrating with life-saving water, )
(they get back to work.)
It's so hot.
The spiciness from the chilli peppers is hitting my face.
It really feels spicy now.
(Sneezing)
- Isn't it because it's spicy?
- Gosh, yes.
(It's so spicy that it makes him sneeze.)
It's hot and spicy. It's total chaos.
What's our goal for today?
- Forty kilograms.
- Forty kilograms?
- Per mesh bag...
- We earn 20 dollars per bag.
(Are you serious?)
I don't think chilli peppers weigh that much.
I think 2 buckets will fill 1 bag.
(Will they be able to harvest 40kg?)
I'm not tired.
Not even a little.
(50 minutes into the chilli pepper harvest)
My brain isn't sending commands to my fingers anymore.
(Because it's too hot)
(Exhaling)
(Turning)
Honey, when are we quitting?
Honey, I want to quit first.
She's possessed.
- Sun Young, what are you saying?
- Honey.
- She's possessed by a baby ghost.
- I'll go back to Seoul first.
- She's possessed by a ghost.
- Goodbye.
- Take care.
- Sun Young.
- Sun Young, are you okay?
- She's possessed by a ghost.
Hey, it's a bee. Go away.
Go away.
- Go away.
- Get away.
- Leave.
(Everyone has lost their mind.)
Eat this before you go.
(Feeling sorry)
Eat this.
Eat it before you go, you punk.
"Eat it before you go?"
(You're scaring me.)
(70 minutes into the labour work)
How is everyone doing? Is it manageable?
It's not manageable.
- It's not, right?
- It's very hard.
Right.
It feels like someone has to collapse before we can finish.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Do you want to do it, Sang Hun?
- What?
Why don't you do it?
Here's what I'll do.
Japan collapsing. The US collapsing.
India collapsing.
Shall I start with the US?
Don't look at him.
Keep working and react when he does it.
Here he goes. Ready, action.
Hey, sun.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh!
(Hollywood-level acting)
(American reactions exploding left and right)
- Oh, my gosh.
- That's okay.
Oh, my gosh.
(Fainting attempt number 2)
That's okay. I'm okay.
(The American man looks quite fragile.)
- That was the US.
- The US.
This is Japan.
(Next is Japan.)
(Breathing)
I feel...
(The rainy road hurts.)
(Everyone bursts out laughing.)
- What about India?
- India.
(Anticipating)
(What is everyone doing without working?)
(Hurry and pick chilli peppers...)
(Hakaiyomo)
(Let's just dance.)
(Laughing)
(Shake it)
(This is exciting.)
Did you do India, Japan, and the US?
I did them all.
- Can you do China too?
- China?
- I forgot about China.
- Yes, China.
China is the land of martial arts.
- Right.
- Yes.
(Exclaiming)
(Speaking Chinese)
(This is the spirit of the Chinese continent.)
(Laughing)
My knees are stinging.
- Seriously...
- Gosh, Sang Hun.
Even in this heat,
he's putting his whole body into it just to make us laugh.
He's so funny.
(Thanks to Sang Hun who went all out to make them laugh)
Once you get into it,
- It gets done fast?
- it's over before you know it.
(The siblings gather their strength and get back to work.)
- Yoon Seo.
- Yes?
- Let me know when you're done.
- Why?
I'll carry yours over there.
Give it to me.
- It's okay.
- I'll take it.
(She refuses once.)
Seriously?
(She reluctantly accepts the offer.)
What if they start having feelings for each other like this?
- Yoon Seo.
- Yes?
I'll make an acrostic poem with "chilli pepper."
"Chili."
Yoon Seo, the prettiest one in the chilli pepper field.
Oh, come on.
My gosh.
Goodness.
(Is this really possible?)
- "Pepper."
- She's pathetic.
(She's pathetic.)
Hey!
(Upset)
Stick to the concept.
I was switching it up.
Yoon Seo, I'll try again.
(Trying again while keeping the flirting concept)
- "Chili."
- Good job, Yoon Seo.
(Will you do it right this time?)
- "Pepper."
- That's pathetic.
(Laughing)
It's not funny.
- Have you been hit with a pepper?
- Comedy is all about repetition.
(The flirtation might turn into a fight.)
- The concept completely fell apart.
- That won't work.
You're not supposed to flirt on a chilli pepper field.
(Laughing)
(Ssang Soon must be very lonely.)
I'm getting the hang of this. I can do it with one hand.
- Are you getting the hang of it?
- Yes.
(Yoon Seo can do it easily with one hand.)
It snaps when I do it. One more.
I can tell just by touching them.
Whether they're ripe or not.
After picking so many, you start to develop a knack for it.
(Although they're covered in sweat)
(Sighing)
(Moaning)
I'll pick one more...
before I collapse.
It's hard, but we have to do it.
Everyone, don't complain just because it's hot.
Summer is supposed to be hot.
(Harvesting without taking a break)
(Picking...)
(and picking)
(Beads of sweat form under their chins.)
It's spicy and hot. It's absolute chaos.
My gosh.
(They keep picking nonstop.)
Gosh, we went far.
(The heat is impossible to get used to.)
I should wait.
(Wiping away the sweat)
(If they grit their teeth and keep pushing until the end)
(Exhaling)
(The chilli peppers pile up in the basket.)
(Pouring after pouring)
(Once they move the last bucket and pour it in)
(They filled 3 baskets after 1 hour and 30 minutes of work.)
It's done. We're done.
We harvested a lot. Don't you think?
Sang Hun is completely drenched.
(He showered in sweat.)
- Come and have some snacks.
- They're calling us for a snack.
- It's a snack.
- Aren't you sweating?
My goodness.
(Sweating bullets)
I didn't even realise that the snack arrived.
There's a snack? That's incredible.
What is it?
Gosh, what's this?
- What is it?
- It looks great.
Gosh, it's something refreshing.
It's leaf mustard.
(A specialty of Yeosu, leaf mustard mul kimchi)
It's leaf mustard with acorn jelly.
(An unusual combination of acorn jelly)
(Leaf mustard mul kimchi with acorn jelly)
(For dessert, a perfectly juicy watermelon)
Gosh, what's this?
(Cold coffee to wash away the fatigue)
This is amazing.
(Sun Young goes straight for the watermelon.)
- Leaf mustard and acorn jelly.
- The watermelon is good.
(She's inhaling it.)
Are you eating dessert already?
(Bursting out laughing)
- You eat dessert first.
- Right.
- Isn't this an appetizer?
- I didn't know that.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
(After the appetizer, it's time to start the meal.)
It looks delicious.
(Taking a spoonful of leaf mustard mul kimchi with acorn jelly)
It's delicious.
(Drinking up the sweet and sour broth from the bowl)
(So refreshing)
So this is leaf mustard kimchi with acorn jelly.
- Leaf mustard with acorn jelly.
- That must be it.
- I never had these together.
- Me neither.
It's so good.
(Jung Ah also takes a refreshing bite.)
(It cools you all the way down to your core.)
That slightly bitter taste of the leaf mustard is...
(There are no words for it.)
The mustard leaf aroma is incredible.
(Slurping in the mustard leaf)
- Is this leaf mustard kimchi?
- Leaf mustard in the summer...
(A refreshing summer specialty from Yeosu)
It must be something like leaf mustard mul kimchi.
It's very good.
(The perfect combo of crisp leaf mustard and chewy acorn jelly)
It's delicious.
Gosh, this is good.
- It's refreshing.
- This is good.
Gosh, this is good.
(You can't imagine how good it is.)
This is really tasty.
(Gulping it down)
(Gulping it down again)
(Glancing)
Did you just finish... the broth in one go?
- I love broth.
- He must love broth.
He finished the broth. Do you want some more?
- I'll give you some more.
- If you leave some...
(Giving a refill to the broth lover)
- Thank you.
- Sure.
(They keep the concept going.)
(Straight to another sip of broth)
- Is it good?
- Yes.
- It's so good.
- It's delicious.
Our kids definitely love Korean food.
- Yes, that's right.
- Yes.
- I've always liked acorn jelly.
- Me too.
- It's very good with leaf mustard.
- I agree.
There's also chilli pepper.
(Whoosh)
- Gosh, the wind is blowing.
- The wind is blowing.
It feels so cool.
(A cool breeze comes by for a moment.)
Just a little breeze feels so good.
Who knew this could make me so happy?
(Taking a little time to relax)
It's delicious.
(Exhausted)
What are we doing after work today?
You'll get your free time.
You're lying.
(Suspicious)
Don't say that. Just trust her.
- Okay. Really?
- Don't say anything.
- That's great.
I'll scold those who come up with ideas today.
- A creek...
- Be quiet!
Creek...
Don't you have many things you want to do?
Me?
- Don't say it.
- Be quiet.
Creek...
You Seok, you only slept two hours last night.
You Seok only got two hours of sleep. He needs some rest.
- Right.
- I'm not saying this for myself.
I'm doing it for you.
I'm okay.
(Really?)
(I'm fine.)
Let's give each other a neck-and-back rinse today.
What's the matter?
(Gasping)
Sure, we can just blur it.
That would be embarrassing.
"Blur it?"
- Seriously.
- It's the same at a bathhouse.
- About being naked...
- Then everyone has to get naked.
- Why should only we get naked?
- Right.
- Then let's all strip...
- After work...
Instant coffee.
Let's stop by a supermarket.
We'll go to the supermarket without washing up.
- Okay.
- What are we having for dinner?
We'll make chicken stew with ripened kimchi that we got last time.
I'd absolutely love that.
Sang Hun, can you make us a dish?
- I can make several if you want.
- Your hidden weapon.
(Anticipating)
We'll go to the supermarket...
- and buy some ingredients.
- Okay.
That sounds great.
Shall we go to the supermarket now? One, two, three. Go.
(The packing starts.)
The snack time is disappearing naturally.
Let's start parking.
- Jung Ah, stay seated.
- Yoon Seo.
- Stay seated.
- Stay seated, Jung Ah.
- I'll do it. Everyone, sit down.
- You can't do everything yourself.
- I want to do it too.
- I'm greedy.
Right. Dex...
- I'll do it. Everyone, sit down.
- You can't do everything yourself.
- I want to do it too.
- I'm greedy.
Right. Dex...
Dex...
(Who?)
(Giving her a look)
(The name slipped out of her mouth.)
(Never mind...)
She said the forbidden name.
(Flustered)
I guess coming to Yeosu makes you think...
about Jae Wook and Dex a lot.
(Kang You Seok)
- If you open it, I'll put them in.
- Okay.
(He calms down and starts packing.)
Fill it up.
(Putting the chilli peppers into the mesh bag)
I'll help you from the side.
- Could you just hold it for me?
- This won't work.
(Sang Hun and Yoon Seo, Sun Young and You Seok)
- They're green.
- Do I leave them out?
Goodness.
(Scoop them up nice and generously and transfer them over)
You're good at packing them.
(A handful)
You have big hands.
(Yoon Seo's all-purpose hands are shining again today.)
We might get ten bags.
- Right? We'll be fine.
- Yes.
There are more than I thought.
(Despite the scorching weather, they harvested a lot.)
(Jung Ah watches the younger ones working.)
His underwear is showing.
(Underwear)
That's probably fashion. People wear them like that on purpose now.
- Sagging?
- Don't you know about sagging?
- I don't know.
- I did it on purpose.
- They show underwear on purpose.
- Really?
- It's a trendy fashion style.
- Then show more of it.
(Sagging)
(Looking away)
How many bags do you have?
We got two bags for now. We have a lot left.
We'll get three bags.
As long as we pack one more...
We harvested a lot.
Did they say 20 dollars per mesh bag?
Twenty dollars.
Oh, my. We earned a lot of money.
We might have more than ten bags.
(There are still so many.)
If we have ten mesh bags,
- we'll make 200 dollars.
- Give it to me.
If we don't have enough...
We didn't expect you to pick so many.
- We worked very hard.
- Why are you always surprised?
We always harvest more than you expect.
That's right.
They're genuinely surprised.
(The siblings became professional hard workers.)
This will be 5kg.
- It might be over 5kg.
- There are so many green ones.
Isn't it exactly 5kg?
(Accurate)
(A human scale that measures exactly 5kg)
This is 5kg.
This is quite a lot too.
(Accurate again)
(Weighing)
This must be 4kg.
Sang Hun is accurate.
(Once the human scale fills the mesh bag)
(Yoon Seo struggles to carry it while sniffling.)
It's 5kg.
(It's accurate without a single gram off.)
(When you aren't sure about the mesh bag's weight)
- Seven...
- Do I have to add more, Sang Hun?
Yes, you have to add more.
- Should I add more here too?
- Yes.
The other one is okay.
If you fill it up to the end without tapping it, it'll be exactly 5kg.
- Okay.
- Yes.
(Their work speed keeps picking up.)
I told you we were good.
I'm the grandson of a farmer.
(The last box is already nearly empty.)
- We reached our target.
- Ten?
Yes.
We got ten bags.
(A big harvest at a glance)
(The last bag of peppers goes on the scale.)
(Packing is done.)
- Good.
- How many bags are there?
- Eleven.
- One, two, three, four...
- Eleven bags.
Eight, nine, ten, eleven.
- It's 55kg.
- They did 11 bags.
- Since it's 55kg...
- We did 55kg.
- It's 55kg.
- How much is that?
Goodness.
Great work on harvesting the peppers.
(Feeling proud)
You're not crying, are you? Don't cry.
You're not crying, are you?
(Handing over the pepper shipping fee)
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten. Nineteen, twenty, twenty-one, twenty-two.
Okay, 220 dollars.
- Nice.
- We must be good at work.
The math checks out.
Shall we move on to the corn field?
(Absolutely!)
- Oh, my.
- Oh, dear.
It was tough, you know?
- Did you harvest many peppers?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- They look tasty.
- There are pepper leaves.
Make them into a side dish.
- It's not much.
- We picked 55kg.
You worked hard.
Good.
- We'll enjoy them.
- Thank you.
- We'll enjoy the peppers.
(The peppers the siblings worked hard to harvest today)
(Soaking up Yeosu's warm sunshine)
(After being processed in various forms)
(Pepper makes our meals even more delicious.)
(Korea's red flavour, chilli peppers)
(Fresh off the Sea)
What's with the snapping?
My gosh, just look at her.
(In the best condition after the hard labour)
You're good.
(Their tops are soaked in sweat.)
- Gosh, we earned a lot.
- The breeze feels nice.
Totally.
- All three of us.
- Sang Hun, do you usually cook?
- That's right.
- Really?
- I'm in charge of everything.
- Amazing.
- Tell me what you want, - Yes?
And I'll make it.
That's so cool.
Tonight's dinner will be done in no time.
It won't take long.
- Let's go.
Look at the fields swaying in the wind.
- It's pretty.
- My gosh.
(The fields roll like waves in the refreshing breeze.)
How pretty.
- It reminds me of the sea.
- You're right.
(The fields roll like waves in the refreshing breeze.)
We're going home
(On the way home with excitement)
(A wetland park catches the siblings' eyes.)
- That's a wetland.
- You're right.
I visited Suncheon Bay, and it was really pretty.
- I...
- Suncheon Bay is beautiful.
I've only been there once,
and it was really pretty. Go check it out.
Dex is from Suncheon.
- Yes, I watched it.
- Is that so?
- He mentioned it.
- His parents still live there.
I'm actually a fan.
- Seriously.
- We should meet up.
When I brought up the idea, Jin Young...
- Idea?
- You know...
- That thing.
- Do you mean the field day?
I mentioned a group camping trip.
I said we should do it if possible,
and he said he wouldn't miss it for the world.
Same here.
What if he wins every game?
Yoon Seo, don't you believe in me?
Really, shouldn't you be on my side?
Team up with Dex. I'm teaming up with Eun Jin.
You're cheap.
You Seok, I didn't mention the name.
I was talking about you.
- Stop being ridiculous.
- Field day shouldn't be...
- all about sports.
- You Seok...
- We should do some brain games.
- I...
- Let's have a game of omok.
- No, listen.
- Brain games on a field day?
- You can't beat Eun Jin...
at omok.
We can't beat Ahn Eun Jin at omok?
Bring it on.
- I...
- We'll win the brain games.
Go against her first.
I'll crush her, Sun Young.
- Do that.
- I'll crush her.
Jung Ah!
- Fine.
- Jung Ah.
I can only be fair, you know?
You're being unfair, saying Eun Jin would win...
- and Dex would win.
- But...
He'll win with one finger.
- My mom...
- This is fun.
You'll be at a disadvantage if Jung Ah is the referee.
Bring it on, Ahn Eun Jin. Are you seeing this?
- I get it.
- I won't lose either.
I'm confident in speed.
(Will the siblings' field day actually happen?)
This road is pretty too.
(A beautiful view after all the commotion)
This place is really nice.
- I know, right?
- Totally.
(Crossing the wide-open Dolsan Bridge)
Jung Ah, you're revisiting that house, right?
- Yes.
- The house you stayed at.
Correct, the house we stayed at last year.
It must bring back so many memories
- Of course.
- Who would've thought...
you'd come back?
Exactly. This is a first.
- Right?
- Revisiting an old house.
- After a year.
- Yes.
It was one of the pretty houses.
(What will the siblings' home look like after a year?)
(Winding up the mountain road)
(A small harbour village lies below.)
Right, it was Seongdu Village.
(Arriving at Seongdu Village, where our house is)
(Amazed)
Goodness, how beautiful.
(Where the wide-open sea stretches out)
(The siblings are back in Seongdu Village.)
Gosh, I'm back.
(Jung Ah slowly looks around the village she visited a year ago.)
How do you feel to be back here after a year, Jung Ah?
But...
It's just...
(Thinker Jung Ah)
- It's really...
- Jung Ah.
- I've been here...
- Try being a feeler.
But I'm not a feeler.
"It's so nice being back here after a year!"
I tried to do that in my head first,
but I just...
- Is that so?
- Yes.
"Right, I remember," and that was it.
(A thinker's feeler moment)
This place is great.
The village is so pretty.
I thought how pretty this tree was while watching the show.
- Like the leaves.
- It's pretty, right?
I bet the tree is super expensive.
(A protected tree that has stood by the front gate for 400 years)
(A year later, it stands strong with even more greenery.)
My goodness, it's such a pretty tree.
Really, this tree.
You can tell it's really old at a glance.
It's beautiful.
(A view that leaves you speechless)
- It lives in such a nice place.
- Just look at the tree.
- It's the siblings'.
- My gosh.
The siblings'.
(The harbour and refreshing open sea unfold right in front of the house.)
(A charming, cosy home...)
(with a magnificent protected tree in the yard)
(Jung Ah enters the house with excitement.)
It hasn't changed.
It hasn't changed
(A place filled with memories for Jung Ah)
I've seen this place on TV.
I've seen this house on TV.
This house is gorgeous.
- How pretty.
- It sure is pretty in person.
It's really pretty.
(A place where new excitement begins for the others)
What a pretty place.
(Back again at the protected-tree house in Yeosu)
Where's our family photo?
- The family photo is here.
- It's over here.
(Even the family photos from Taean have made the move.)
That's our family photo.
(Laughing)
It's a themed-family photo.
(Looking like a family with quite a story to tell)
It's giving off late 1980s and early 1990s vibes.
(Pure 6090 vibes)
(Still just as striking)
(After all the unpacking is done)
No, our You Seok.
What pretty flowers.
(Another day with You Seok's flowers at the siblings' home.)
(Peace returns after a long time, with flowers.)
Are we too dirty from not showering?
Will the viewers find it unpleasant?
It should be okay, right?
Dear viewers. We dried off with the AC.
Our sweat isn't that dirty.
Gosh, I'm loving it.
Is it still hot here?
Yes, it's still hot.
(On her back)
(Meanwhile, Yoon Seo got changed.)
(She spotted Sun Young.)
(Yoon Seo naturally goes near her...)
(and uses Sun Young's arm as a pillow.)
(Finding her cute)
You just daze at the leaves.
- Right, Sun Young?
- Yes.
This house is really nice.
(Spaced out)
I feel like we're in a TV right now.
(Under the refreshing shade of the protected tree)
(The wind blows softly and slowly.)
(In the afternoon, villagers take a break in the shade.)
The tree is everything.
(The siblings also enjoy a peaceful rest beneath the protected tree.)
I'm loving this place.
- Just look at the tree.
- The tree makes it better.
I know, right? It's the view from right here.
(Just lying down and looking at the tree is healing.)
How do you feel about the show ending...
when we're about to get the hang of it?
- Hang of it? Hang of what?
- Yes?
- We've grown close, - Yes?
- so I can go all out more.
- I see.
But it's our last trip. How do you feel about it?
(Before they know it, it's the last trip.)
It's such a shame.
This will all become good memories.
I lived in a rural area after elementary school,
and it had a similar atmosphere.
This place is amazing. It's best to live somewhere nice.
(Soft, dreamy vibes)
- Right?
- It's getting too close.
(Hi.)
Hi.
What kind of concept is this?
Do you want to hang out together?
(The youngest hamming it up for the camera.)
(Meanwhile, Sang Hun returns after changing clothes.)
I'm the only one who hasn't changed yet, right?
(Laughing)
(Getting up)
I'll go get changed.
(While Sun Young is taking a shower)
- Should we take a selfie, Jung Ah?
- Yes, let's take one together.
Okay.
I'll take one.
I'll take some photos of you too.
Really, I want to...
In 1, 2, 3.
(Busy making memories today)
It's for Instagram.
My daughter told me no peace sign.
- What? Why?
- No peace sign? Why?
- In 1, 2...
- Do this instead.
(A toothache patient)
(A cheek heart for a toothache)
I have to learn from Yoon Seo how to look away.
Looking away?
She always looks away when taking photos.
I do. I look into the distance like this.
(The standard)
They have too many rules.
There's even a head shot.
- Are you good at taking photos?
- No.
I'm not used to taking pictures.
Me neither.
I'll take photos of Jung Ah.
(Yoon Seo was listening to the two.)
- Jung Ah.
- Yes?
You look so pretty right now.
- Right now?
- Yes.
With the flower behind.
A little to this side.
- This side.
- Do I look away?
A little more to this side.
(But Jung Ah doesn't know where to look.)
I become awkward again.
- Drink the coffee.
- I need to look away. Drink it?
(Much more natural after adding an item)
Gorgeous. I'm serious.
(Learning the latest trends, Coffee is just for show.)
(Eyes on. Now I'm one of the young crowd.)
(You Seok was watching from the side.)
Jung Ah, this is the Instagram vibe.
Wear this for the photos.
(A new item, the winnowing basket sitting nearby)
Why wear that?
Instagram?
(A new trendsetter emerges)
- Take one wearing it.
- It'll look cute.
Put it on your head.
Really? Is it the Instagram vibe?
(Intrigued)
- Take one wearing it.
- It'll look cute.
Put it on your head.
- Like this?
- Yes.
Drink the coffee like it's no biggie.
That's it.
How adorable!
(Photographer Roh is somehow very excited.)
(A cutie)
Jung Ah, it's great. You look so cute.
It's so cute.
- It's the current trend.
- You're serious, right?
Of course.
- Yes.
- Of course.
Jung Ah.
(The siblings have great teamwork in such situations.)
- Don't you trust me?
- You know your stuff.
(This is the latest vibe, right?)
How about making potato jeon...
as a snack?
- Is there a portable gas stove?
- Yes.
You've got to eat as you make the jeon.
- As you cook the jeon?
- Yes.
Potato jeon doesn't take long.
All you need is starch.
- While making the jeon?
- Yes.
- You eat it while making it?
- It won't take long.
(Source: Jeong Sang Hun, No Jeong Sang Hun)
(From dishes for the children)
(Korean, Chinese, Western, Japanese, and street food)
(There's nothing he can't cook.)
It becomes fluffy like a cloud and tastes amazing.
(A sexy catfish who cooks)
- The potato slicer.
- With thinly sliced potatoes?
It's best to use a food slicer.
True, and we have one.
- A food slicer will do.
- You keep the starch.
- Yes.
- Just add a bit of flour and cook.
Exactly.
With the red peppers we received,
let's make the dipping sauce. It'll be perfect.
- With crushed peppers.
- Nice.
Stay here.
- Will you cook it?
- It'll be done in 15 minutes.
- Really? Then cook for us.
- Fifteen minutes is all I need.
Really? Then we'll all chill.
- Go ahead.
- We'll all lie down.
Okay, I can take my time.
All I need is a food slicer.
(Sang Hun heads into the kitchen...)
(and starts peeling potatoes right away.)
(The potatoes are peeled in no time.)
- All that's necessary is here.
- Yes.
(With his experience, he finds the food slicer.)
(Starts slicing the potatoes into strips)
(Potato strips in an instant)
(The cooking flows effortlessly.)
(Starch)
(Seasoned salt)
(He starts mixing it after seasoning lightly.)
(Mixing)
I'll do it.
(Sang Hun leaves the rest to You Seok.)
(Mixing)
(He cleans up as he goes.)
(Sang Hun heads to the kitchen with something.)
- We...
- What is that?
I brought soy sauce from home. It's tsuyu.
- Is it an all-purpose soy sauce?
- It's tsuyu.
I made tsuyu at home.
(It's homemade tsuyu too.)
(Making tsuyu lemon sauce for the potato jeon)
A bit of tsuyu, and then some lemon juice.
(Lemon juice)
Add a bit of cooking wine.
(Cooking wine for extra umami)
(A sauce made in no time, all by eye)
(Taste test)
It's good.
Add in some chilli peppers, and it's done.
I just place them on top, right?
Add some chilli peppers, please.
It's so fresh.
(Chopping up the fresh peppers harvested today)
That must be the dipping sauce.
This much should do, right?
(Super-speedy tsuyu lemon sauce is ready.)
I remember now. In this room,
we prepped for the birthday party.
"Hey, Jae Wook." We did it right here.
(The former younger siblings are brought up again today.)
Jung Ah.
I remember now. In this room,
we prepped for the birthday party.
"Hey, Jae Wook." We did it right here.
(The former younger siblings are brought up again today.)
Jung Ah.
I'm sorry.
Please don't bring up memories...
you had with other guys.
I'm the jealous type.
(A big blow)
Only talk about me in front of me, please.
(Okay.)
(Only look at me.)
(The former head chef comes into the kitchen looking for work.)
Who wants this?
- What is it?
- Me.
- What we bought at the supermarket.
- I'm in.
- We...
- Since it's duck,
let's have some onion as a side dish.
Right?
- It's a must.
- With Sang Hun here with us,
I've got nothing to do.
- Really, Sang Hun.
- Jung Ah, get some rest.
(Take a break while you can!)
He does everything without being asked.
(Thanks to him, Jung Ah is happily unemployed.)
(Clean onions...)
(go onto the food slicer for pickled onions.)
(He slices the onion at super speed.)
(Cooking skills honed by experience)
(Sang Hun's pickled onion recipe)
This is oligosaccharide.
Soy sauce.
(Yangjo soy sauce)
A bit of tsuyu.
(Sang Hun's pickled onion recipe:)
(Oligosaccharide, yangjo soy sauce, tsuyu, vinegar)
(Add the right amount and stir)
(A quick pickled onion sauce for smoked duck is ready.)
- Pour some on and eat.
- Onions.
- It's pickled onion.
- You know what's good.
It just needs to be cooked now.
- I'll get some water.
- Let me.
(Sang Hun finished the potato jeon prep in just 10 minutes.)
Jeong Sang Hun is unbelievable.
- He's literally a chef.
- Right?
We have a chef guest.
- He's on another level.
- Our guest is extraordinary.
For real.
Doctor.
Doctor?
Doctor!
Yes?
(Jeong Sang Hun, A cooking expert)
Should I cook the jeon?
- Go ahead.
- Yes, sir.
(Coating the pan generously with oil)
(Now let's fry the jeon!)
(Sun Young is on pancake duty, hands up.)
(Added starch water)
(The starch water helps bind it together.)
(Keep frying the jeon)
(Give the potato jeon a good shake so it doesn't stick.)
(The edges are golden brown before you know it.)
- Doctor.
- Yes?
I'd appreciate it if you'd tell me when to flip the jeon.
- When should I flip it?
- Flip it.
- Now?
- Yes, flip it.
- Okay.
- It's done.
You should pour plenty of oil.
(Crispy edges mean it's time to flip.)
- Flip it.
- Here I go.
- That's it.
- Amazing.
- It looks good.
- Gosh.
- Flip it.
- Here I go.
That's it.
(Golden-brown, crispy potato jeon)
Look.
- It looks good.
- It smells incredible.
Awesome.
(The delicious aroma fills the entire house.)
(Sizzling)
(The enchanting sizzling sound)
- It feels like a national holiday.
- Look at this.
- Right?
- Yes.
- It looks so delicious.
- It feels like a holiday...
since I'm cooking jeon.
Cook it as if you were deep-frying it.
Like deep-frying it. Got it.
(Using the turner to press it down on both sides to make it crispier)
- It sticks nicely.
- Yes.
It looks delicious.
- It's...
- This is it.
(Potato jeon is complete with the holiday vibe.)
- Potato jeon looks so pretty.
- Right, it's so pretty.
It looks good. We just need to bring makgeolli now.
Should we be eating so much for snack?
(That's a generous amount for snacks.)
This is incredible.
(With Sang Hun's tsuyu lemon sauce)
(Lean smoked duck from the supermarket)
(And sweet pickled onions which goes perfectly with duck)
Local makgeolli.
(Accompanied with cool and fresh Yeosu makgeolli)
- The potatoes are really big.
- Yes.
(Sun Young will continue to cook.)
Gosh, I didn't do anything.
It's my first time eating a meal which I didn't do anything.
Exactly. Times like this...
Good job picking chillies.
- Good job.
- I need to cook potato jeon.
- Potato jeon.
Join us first.
(Drinking)
(Satisfied)
(Sang Hun who worked hard to cook takes a sip.)
(He swallows down the exhaustion with the drink.)
The makgeolli is so good.
- I like this makgeolli.
- The makgeolli is great.
(Once they've quenched their thirst...)
It looks chewy.
It's perfect.
- You just eat it like this. Nice.
- Yes, just like this.
(Sang Hun tries the potato jeon without the sauce.)
(Humming)
- The potato tastes amazing.
- The potato.
It'll taste good as is too.
It's already seasoned, so you don't need the sauce.
(Crispy outside, chewy inside, potato jeon tastes great as is, )
- Sorry.
- Dip it in this.
(but dip it in sweet and sour tsuyu lemon sauce.)
This is crazy.
(Straight into her mouth)
(Frowning because it's so good)
It's so good.
(The sauce goes perfectly with potato jeon.)
This.
The lemon flavour in the soy sauce tastes amazing.
(The sauce's faint lemon flavour spreads after the savoury taste.)
- With the soy sauce.
- Have it with the duck.
(Yoon Seo dips it in the tsuyu lemon sauce.)
(In one bite)
(Surprised)
(She follows it with a sip of makgeolli.)
(It's a perfect combo.)
- I will... You're fast.
- Sun Young.
I was going to go.
(A delivery service for Sun Young who's seated far away to cook)
It tastes good plain.
(He blows it to cool it down.)
(Straight into her mouth)
(Her eyes open wide.)
You know,
I smell some scent from the jeon. What scent is it?
- You're right.
- It smells like flower...
- Oh, it's potato scent.
- Potatoes must have a scent too.
Potato scent.
- Potatoes have a scent.
- The potatoes...
- were really high quality.
- Shredded potatoes...
have a stronger scent than ground ones.
It's fragrant.
The potatoes are tasty.
(Containing all the fragrance of the potatoes which are in season)
You're supposed to have it with this.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Freshly-cooked potato jeon's humble yet addictive taste)
It's so good.
(Next, they try pickled onions and smoked duck.)
It's tasty.
(Jung Ah places sweet and sour pickled onions on lean duck.)
- It's so good.
(Chewy and crunchy)
(The tasty food makes her smile.)
This is interesting too. Potatoes and onions...
(Potato jeon smell fills the air, and delicious food fills the table.)
They're the same.
(Happy snack time)
Where did you study cooking, Doctor?
- I was in the States for a bit.
- In the States?
Is this American potato jeon?
- Yes, well, it's French Fries.
- French Fries?
(Aunt Jennica from the US likes it.)
I see.
(The cooking master studied in the US.)
- She's started to make a big one.
- This is the last one.
(Golden brown)
(This is the last potato jeon.)
It looks so good.
(Flipping the last potato jeon)
Yes!
(Cheering)
(Feeling proud)
Oh, my gosh.
Ever since she's made...
hundreds of jeons for the elderly last time,
- she's become...
- She's the goddess of jeon.
- a jeon master.
- I've been good at it since before.
(Master Kim Jeon Young has become the goddess of jeon.)
Here comes the next one.
(Freshly-cooked hot potato jeon)
(They fill up their stomachs with delicious food...)
(and relieve today's fatigue.)
It's nice.
(The siblings spend a relaxing afternoon.)
When will we draw the mural?
(What mural?)
This wall? Is it the one in front?
(What are they talking about?)
(The story started a month ago.)
- This time, - Yes.
Why don't we draw a mural?
Decorate the village and so on.
You must get the permission of the villagers.
We will.
Some of the villages we went had really pretty murals.
- Hadong had them.
- Hadong, yes.
The first place had murals too.
(They welcomed the siblings with open arms.)
- Murals were really nice.
- They were.
I'm really bad at drawing.
- Sun Young and you...
- I'm bad at it too.
- She can draw, and we can paint.
- I'm bad at painting too.
- You can draw.
- Painting is easy.
There was a time when I only drew. Nowadays, not so much.
I draw anything and everything.
There's a limit to how well I can draw.
This is my favourite among the recent ones,
so I hung it in my living room.
I just wing it.
(Jung Ah knew about Sun Young's passion for drawing.)
I have so many things I want to draw,
but I don't know how.
Yoon Seo must be able to do it all since she learned how.
Why would we need to draw there anyway?
(Right on point)
We ask what kind of style the villagers want...
and decorate the village accordingly.
It sounds amazing. We can do it while Yoon Seo is here.
Let's make full use of her.
(Make full use of the art student.)
(The art student is full of worries.)
Will you paint the background before drawing?
I need to check the wall first.
(Where Yoon Seo pointed...)
(has murals lined up next to the breakwater.)
(From a cute mural of sea creatures swimming...)
(to a mural with the lives of the fishing village)
I hear there's an empty spot on the wall.
They're lending it to us?
Yes. There so happens to be one empty spot.
It'll be nice to fill it up.
- The villagers would like it.
- We'll do it tomorrow afternoon.
Shall we go?
(Let's go to the wall where the siblings will paint on.)
A mural.
(Excited and nervous)
Which way should we go?
- It's really pretty.
- The stones...
(They explore the village as they walk.)
They're pretty.
(Various colours blend in together to create a warm atmosphere.)
That's the spot.
- The wall is pretty long.
- It's wide.
- That's...
- An hour or two won't cut it.
- It won't.
- This is practically work.
Exactly.
(That's a huge wall.)
It's big.
This...
(It makes the siblings look like figures.)
Goodness.
(This wall is 13 by 1.5 meters.)
(To estimate the size...)
(A canvas as big as a grown woman, 150 by 110 centimetres)
(12 such canvases can fit.)
When will we finish this?
Should we sketch it today?
- They even coloured the background.
- Goodness.
(Next to the siblings' wall, )
(a mural is already in place.)
- Is it possible?
- I have no idea.
(Although the colours have faded, there are five background colours.)
But...
if we're drawing at this level,
- it can be done quickly.
- It'll be fast.
- Really?
- Yes.
- This won't take so long.
- It won't.
Really?
We shouldn't draw something so detailed.
Exactly. Draw them big.
- Like this.
- Yes.
With seaweed?
Just this.
(They aren't thugs.)
I think we should draw something...
in continuation of this mural.
We should connect the waves.
Yes, the sea.
We'll paint it in a way...
that looks similar to the faded painting.
That boat looks nice.
- A boat... Right.
- I'll draw a boat.
Let's draw dolphins and a few fish.
Sun Young, sketch the fish.
Sang Hun, you can draw an octopus or something, right?
Yes, I can.
Just this level.
(The siblings will draw the mural to form one sea.)
I'll draw the waves first.
We'll paint the background first and let it dry.
We'll draw the boat and so on tomorrow.
Today, Sang Hun and I will cook.
- You guys...
- Okay.
Sang Hun and I will cook.
You guys work on the mural here.
We'll paint the background.
Tomorrow, we'll all come and paint on top of it tomorrow.
Yes, it needs to dry.
Let's start something today.
I'm grateful.
We don't need to use black like them for the waves.
- What should I do?
- The waves...
- Differently?
- Yes.
Pick three cool colours.
Then I'll paint a gradient at the end.
(More serious than ever)
(What will this wall turn into?)
It's my first time doing work on such a big scale.
(Filling up the wide wall)
That's such a nice colour.
(The siblings' hands)
It uses up a lot of your energy.
Did you all learn art?
(Fresh off the Sea, their mural-painting challenge)
Let me check the draft.
(Time to prepare before painting on the wall)
The draft...
(Yoon Seo is coming up with a draft.)
I've never drawn ever since I've graduated.
I never drew. Don't expect so much from me.
This is so hard for me too.
I'm not an illustrator. I studied fine art.
I've never drawn an illustration.
Poor Yoon Seo.
(They're holding back their laughter because Yoon Seo is so cute.)
I feel so pressured when I think about how it'd last forever.
(The more she wants to do well, the more pressured she feels.)
(She still checks the draft while she's stressed.)
- Let's go.
This will be fun.
(No more worrying, let's get going.)
(Walking)
- Doctor.
- Yes?
Good luck.
- We'll get going.
- We'll go and do some art.
- You know, art...
- Yes.
(Doctor Jeong Sang Hun's introduction to art)
I don't know what you think about it,
but you shouldn't take it lightly.
- Okay.
I'm not done talking.
I'm not done talking. Don't leave.
What you're thinking,
- Beyond...
- and what you insist on.
- Yes.
- Get rid of those thoughts.
- That's not it.
- Get rid of them?
I was about to bring those thoughts with me.
- Don't. Get rid of them.
- Get rid of them? Okay.
At times, you need to listen to those younger than you.
Of course.
And...
we shouldn't take responsibility.
(Part 3. Don't take responsibility.)
- If possible...
- Avoiding responsibility?
- If possible, don't take...
- Avoid responsibility?
- That's such an important point.
- Exactly.
- As expected.
- As expected from a doctor.
An American doctor is different.
- He's from the US?
- I understand.
- I'll get going.
- Take it easy.
- I will. I won't take...
- See you.
Any responsibility.
- Just breathe loudly.
We're off to do some art.
I won't take any responsibility.
(The mural expedition leaves with a firm resolve.)
It's going to be so fun.
I can't believe I'm drawing on this show.
Me too.
This is so much more fun than cooking.
It's fun.
I really like looking at different colours.
- Right? So I...
- Yes, making colours.
Whenever I go to an art store, I want to buy...
every pretty colour.
Have you ever drawn?
I'm a complete stranger to it.
(I hope you two become close today.)
Why am I nervous?
(On the other hand, Sun Young can't stop smiling.)
I like this 100 times more than cooking.
Me too. I'm 100 times more useful.
I get to enjoy the luxury.
Contemporary art changes depending on how you interpret it.
I'm thinking of quitting my job and becoming a painter.
I'm detailed.
I'll pour my soul into my art.
(Today's mural plan)
Yoon Seo, do an overall sketch of the waves.
(1. Draw the sketch of the waves. 2. Colour the background.)
(Painter Roh will do the sketch.)
That's fascinating. What is it?
- A chalk.
- That's a chalk?
- Yes.
- Here.
- I guess you draw the sketch...
with a chalk.
Four... One, two, three, four. Okay.
- I'll just draw.
- Yes.
(She goes straight to the wall without hesitation.)
(She takes a glance...)
(and starts drawing.)
(She glances...)
(and draws.)
(She's pretty good.)
(The time taken for her to reach the middle of the 13m-width wall)
(Only 30 seconds)
Okay.
(Walking proudly)
You Seok, pass me a white chalk.
(You Seok, as thoughtful as ever, has the next chalk ready.)
(She draws the remaining part faster!)
(Sun Young and You Seok open the paints first.)
- Yellow.
- White.
It smells so nice.
- Does it?
- Yes.
(Waves are created with each stroke.)
I'm done with the sketch.
(The waves sketch is complete in the blink of an eye!)
How will you colour it?
(2. Paint the background and let it dry.)
Let's mix the paints.
(You can create the colour you want by mixing the paints.)
(Normally, you use 3 to 5 basic colours.)
- We'll mix the paints here...
- Okay.
And colour the wall using rollers.
Tell me what to do. Where should I pour it?
- Here?
- Stop.
- Do I mix it?
- A bit of white. Stop.
(Depending on the ratio of the mix, the colour changes completely.)
- I'll look nice to paint like this.
- Exactly.
It...
It has a gradient.
Like this.
It's pretty. I love it.
- Without mixing them.
- It's pretty.
I like this. It looks like real waves.
(Like white foams on the blue sea)
It's so pretty.
This shouldn't take long. I'll do it.
Okay. Bring me the big one.
I'll make the colour for the wave on top.
You can use both the brush and the roller.
I'll be really quick.
(She paints excitedly following the wave sketch.)
I'm excited.
This is so fun.
(My own sea)
It's been so long. I'm so excited.
(Sun Young is on a roll.)
Can you fill up the empty spots?
- I'll paint there again after this.
- Okay.
(Empty patches)
(Grunting)
(The path to an artist isn't easy.)
I'll be bold and add more.
(Meanwhile, to the blue paint, which will serve as the base)
- What colour are you making?
- Cyan.
Cyan?
Can you use this to paint the second wave?
Will do. It's going to be fun.
(Kang Vinci gets to work too.)
(He carefully makes his first stroke.)
- It's fun, right?
- It is.
It's like I'm colouring a colouring book.
You're good at it.
Painting is easy.
(He's doing well.)
(Yoon Seo finishes mixing the third colour...)
(and starts painting.)
(Although she mixed the same colours, the resulting colour is different!)
I'm sweating.
(With their own blue, )
(they're colouring the waves.)
This is so fun.
Let me retouch it now.
- It'll be finished soon, right?
- Yes.
(After 1 hour of painting, the wall is filled with colours.)
(Meanwhile, Sun Young, who was quietly staring at the wall...)
- You know what, Yoon Seo?
- Yes?
Let's paint over this.
This...
(She suddenly suggests to paint over what they've been doing?)
We went a bit insane with colours for a while.
The colours are too similar, so this doesn't stand out...
- from afar.
- Right? They're too...
This doesn't stand out.
(They're supposed to be different waves.)
Because there's green,
it could look like a mountain.
- Gosh, this is so pretty!
- Right?
- I want to use it as is.
- Me too.
- We should use one colour.
- Should I mix them?
Were we too ambitious?
It's okay. We pursued our dreams.
- Nice.
- Yes, that's it.
(They cheer each other on and pick up the pace.)
That's nice. Keep it up.
(You just need to paint it over!)
The sun is too strong.
Exactly.
(They've been working for 1 hour under the hot sun over 30°C.)
(But none of them show their struggles.)
(The three siblings do their best.)
We should show this to Jung Ah and Sang Hun later.
(They pick up the pace excitedly.)
(The summer sun hangs on the rocky mountain.)
(It's evening in Seongdu Village.)
(Kim Hwa Yeob's home)
I used fresh Yeosu gizzard shad.
I use a lot.
(Another handful of raw gizzard shad!)
Slice radish...
and put it in with perilla leaves.
And add some peppers.
(And the red flavour?)
Red peppers.
(Yeosu red peppers!)
Chojang.
(Put spicy and sweet chojang on it.)
Mix them.
(Mix them well.)
It's seasoned raw gizzard shad.
(Yeosu seasoned raw gizzard shad)
And in summer,
I add various fruits and vegetables.
I picked the loquats and made it myself.
(Add handmade loquat syrup.)
Add water.
(Add cold water.)
It's cold cucumber soup.
(Sloshing cold cucumber soup is complete!)
(What is summer known for?)
My neighbour grew these themselves.
(Corns, of course!)
Add the kernels.
(Pan-fried chewy kernels)
It's corn jeon.
(Chewy and savoury corn jeon!)
(A colourful dinner of Yeosu's summer)
(Seasoned raw gizzard shad, bitter lettuce kimchi, corn jeon, )
(purple rice with beans, red pepper cold cucumber soup)
(What are the siblings' first dinner back in Yeosu?)
Two of us will cook whatever for dinner.
Tell me what you need, and I'll prepare the ingredients.
It's okay, you can be in charge of a dish.
Just the main dishes.
(The dinner will have only the main dishes?)
Dried radish leaf soup.
Ripened kimchi chicken stew.
I'll use the ripened kimchi the elders in Hadong gave us.
- Will you make the soup?
- Yes, I'll make the soup.
I'll boil the chicken first.
- Let me clean this.
- Give me that.
Let's prepare the ingredients all at once...
- and cook everything.
- Right.
- Bring all the ingredients there...
- Yes.
And chop everything.
Okay.
We should cook rice, right?
Yes.
(He's already taking out the rice pot.)
(Sang Hun takes out the pot smoothly.)
Where's the rice?
Check down there.
(He confidently opens the rice container.)
(And he gently scoops up the rice.)
(When he moves it, )
(he does it cheerfully.)
Do that first. I'll throw this.
(He was going to turn on the tab for Jung Ah.)
(Thanks to Jung Ah, he washes the rice to his heart's content.)
(With practised ease, )
(he washes every grain of rice!)
(Jung Ah was walking past behind him.)
Can you give me some rice water?
- Do you want it? Okay.
- I could use it.
Just a bit of rice water.
(For Jung Ah who wants to use rice water to cook)
- Is this enough?
- That's enough.
I'll put it here.
(He places rice water in one corner of the kitchen.)
Let me take out what we'll be using today.
- Are you going to add beef brisket?
- Yes, I am.
And mix doenjang and gochujang together.
- Yes.
- And some garlic.
- I'll mix doenjang and gochujang.
- Okay.
(Wrapping up the dishes, wrapping up the table clean up)
(From the workflow to the recipes, everything flows so smoothly.)
Why do I move slowly when it's hot?
- I am slow.
- Yes, you have to move slowly.
If I move quickly, it's hot.
(Grabbing)
(I take it slow, but I don't stop moving.)
(Nonchalantly...)
(he gets the rice started.)
(Jung Ah grabs the ingredients casually too.)
(Upon seeing that, Sang Hun goes to the fridge.)
(They look at each other...)
(and switch over with a turn.)
I'll use two potatoes.
Okay.
- They love potatoes.
- Right.
(He is fast with the potatoes.)
(Must-haves for a chicken stew!)
(He peels the potatoes and carrot mercilessly.)
(He chops off the top of the onion...)
(and peels it.)
(He peels the green onion with bare hands...)
(and removes the dried part.)
(The fearless cooking genius prepares the dried radish leaves.)
(After checking the outside, )
(he bites and tears open...)
(the package.)
(Of course, he rinses the dried radish leaves thoroughly.)
(He quickly takes the ingredients that need to be chopped outside.)
- Chop the dried radish leaves.
- I'm going to chop them.
Yes, I am.
(Neat and tidy)
Do I use all of those dried radish leaves?
Or should I use half of it?
Am I cooking just for us, or for the staff too?
When you're on this show, you use everything you have.
Okay.
- I'll boil it in a big pot.
- Yes.
(Sang Hun looks for a big pot right away.)
They only got small pots over there, right?
No, there's a big one here.
This one.
(Fortunately, he found a big pot.)
(Relieved)
I need to parboil the chicken.
(She grabs a big pot for the chicken stew too.)
(She boils the water to parboil the chicken first.)
(Heavy)
(In the meantime, this is what she prepares quickly.)
(Amazed)
(The ripened kimchi they got from Maegye Village, Hadong)
- It's incredible.
- As for this part,
cut off the tip so that we can tear it easily later.
Goodness. It looks so good.
- The Napa cabbage kimchi.
- Okay.
(Waiting for the ripened kimchi in a hurry)
(The siblings' tip!)
(Make cuts at the base of kimchi...)
Like this.
(to tear it apart easily later on.)
You can tear it apart easily after cutting it like this.
(Right after getting a big piece of kimchi...)
Should we use one more chunk?
- This is...
- We have 2.2kg of chicken.
- Do we? Is it 2.2kg?
- Yes.
- Two chunks will do, then.
(Finally, she gets another whole head of kimchi.)
- It looks so good. Let me try it.
- I know.
(She tries a piece, unable to resist it.)
I'll try the tip of it.
(Satisfied)
(Slurping)
It's crazy.
- It's so tasty.
- It has a refreshing, fizzy taste.
It ripened perfectly. Goodness.
(Perfect kimchi with maximum fizz to enchant people)
(As for this ripened kimchi, )
(you just have to feel it.)
It's probiotics itself.
It really whets my appetite.
It's so good.
- It tastes really good.
- Really. It's just how I like it.
(He grabs the ripened kimchi and delivers it to Jung Ah.)
(But when she sees that kimchi, )
The ripened kimchi is crazy.
(she's enticed by it again.)
(Right. I can't be like this right now.)
Gosh.
(I need to make the chicken stew with the hefty 2.2kg chicken.)
When will the water start to boil?
- Be careful with your hands.
- Okay.
Here's your onion.
(I'll make it quickly thanks to Sang Hun.)
(The vegetables for the chicken stew are chopped in no time.)
Yes. It's boiling now.
I just need to parboil it.
(She uncovers two packets of the chicken and puts them down.)
(Opening)
(She adds soju first to remove raw chicken's foul smell.)
I think I can remove the foul smell with that much.
(But since it's a lot of chicken, she'll use a whole bottle.)
(Finally, she adds the chicken to the water.)
How many kilograms is this?
(She's putting it in forever.)
It's going to be so good with rice.
(Abundant)
(She stirs everything around, so all pieces are cooked evenly.)
(The chicken has turned white before they knew it.)
- Sang Hun, please pour them...
- Okay.
Over here.
I'll pour them over here.
(After parboiled in soju and water, they don't smell bad, )
(and the meat is plump and juicy.)
After parboiling it,
I wash off the impurities with cold water.
(With cold water, )
Clean it thoroughly.
(she washes it thoroughly one more time.)
I'll drain it, season it, and put it in there.
Then I just need to boil it.
(It's waiting to be seasoned.)
Goodness.
(The cooking genius is shopping for sauces in the meantime.)
They even have dried herring.
- Dried herring?
- Yes. We'll use it with anchovies.
They are perfect for the broth, aren't they?
- The sauces are...
- I put the sauces over here.
- Okay.
- Use whatever you need.
- I need to make the broth.
- Okay.
Gosh. Look at these dried herring.
(He finally starts...)
(to make the beef brisket and dried radish leaf soup.)
(First, he adds the dried herring with refreshing umami.)
(A must for broth!)
(Anchovies for broth and kelp)
(Bring the rich broth to simmer for a while.)
- Do you need my help?
- No.
We just need to season it...
- and bring it to a boil.
- Yes. And we're done.
We'll be done.
(She makes the seasoning sauce for a huge batch of chicken stew.)
(Recipe for the seasoning sauce)
(2 tablespoons of minced garlic, 1 tablespoon of gochujang)
(2 tablespoons of gochujang)
(2.5 tablespoons of gochujang)
(About 4 tablespoons of soy sauce and cooking wine!)
- We don't have ginger syrup.
- No, it's ginger cooking wine.
- Do we have ginger cooking wine?
- Yes.
(The cooking genius found the ginger cooking wine instead.)
Say when.
Just pour it a little.
That's good.
(2 seconds of ginger cooking wine, instead of ginger syrup)
(And as for the chilli powder in charge of spiciness, )
(add plenty of it.)
(2 tablespoons of doenjang to remove the foul smell)
(Oligosaccharide to add sweetness)
(The seasoning sauce is getting ready.)
You're done.
Should I add some pepper?
(She adds some pepper.)
Why doesn't it come out?
(Tilting her head with the stubborn pepper shaker)
Only a little pepper is coming out.
(Laughing)
(Jung Ah.)
Say when to stop.
(Sang Hun adds the pepper after opening it completely.)
- Okay. That's good.
- Okay.
- I love pepper.
- Me too. I love it.
- Let's add more later.
- Yes.
- I don't know...
- I love...
- if this will be enough.
- the pepper scent.
(She dips her finger in the sauce for a quick taste.)
(Satisfied)
Is it good? Let me taste it.
Consider that kimchi is seasoned too.
(Satisfied)
- I like it.
- It's good. Yes.
I didn't add any MSGs.
- Do you want me to?
- No.
It's perfectly balanced.
- This is good enough, right?
- Yes.
It doesn't have that unpleasant aftertaste.
I love it.
(The subtle flavour keeps growing on him.)
It has a hint of sweetness too.
(Jung Ah's...)
(seasoning sauce for the chicken stew is ready!)
- It's drained.
- Okay.
(She grabs the drained chicken.)
(Grunting)
I should do it in the shade.
(She sits down with confidence.)
(Is she adding the sauce right away?)
(She pours the sauce into the parboiled chicken.)
(Jung Ah mixes the chicken with the sauce.)
(Generous Jung Ah...)
(mixes the sauce thoroughly...)
The chicken needs to absorb the sauce.
(with 2.2kg of chicken.)
(Then she grabs a huge pot for the chicken stew.)
(When you mix the chicken with the sauce in advance, )
(it absorbs the sauce well even when you cook a huge batch.)
It looks good.
(It looks tasty to her too.)
(And she covers it evenly...)
(with the onion.)
(The blanket of onion will lock in all the juices.)
- That will be the best one.
- It's crazy.
(Amazed)
This kimchi is insane.
(The ripened kimchi from Maegye Village, Hadong)
(The kimchi juice is a must.)
(2.2kg of chicken and a whole head of kimchi)
(The pot is filled and visually stunning.)
Goodness. It looks delicious already.
Yes. The water from rinsing rice.
That's great.
I'll add more water as I cook it.
It won't taste good if it's too watery.
(The rice water reduces order and boosts flavours.)
(She opens the bottle of water boldly.)
- Pour in just enough water.
- Yes.
Right?
(She covers the pot with the lid...)
(and lets the chicken stew simmer.)
(Sang Hun quietly sits in the back...)
(to prepare the shiitake mushrooms for the soup.)
(He grabs a handful of dried radish leaves, )
(the main ingredient of the soup.)
(Chopping roughly)
(What's the cooking genius's recipe...)
(for beef brisket and dried radish leaf soup?)
(From the broth he cooked in advance...)
(made with dried herring, soup anchovies, and kelp, )
(he takes the chunks out.)
(Then he adds the vegetables he prepped.)
It'll taste really good with the mushrooms.
- Right?
- Yes.
These shiitake mushrooms were cheap.
(It looks delicious.)
(Then he adds a little bit of gochujang, )
(a little bit of minced garlic, )
(and a little bit of salted shrimp.)
(Lastly, as for doenjang, )
(he grabs a big spoonful.)
(Breaking up the lumps of doenjang)
Cooking is all about getting the right saltiness.
- You're right.
- It's all about the seasoning.
(After watching him for a while...)
How old were you when you started cooking?
- Me?
- Yes.
(Starting a beat)
I started cooking when I was...
in sixth grade.
(The cooking genius started cooking when he was a 6th grader.)
(Since you were in elementary school?)
I grew up with my grandmother.
Did you help your grandmother?
She couldn't stand up.
So I stood up and used the stove.
You've cooked...
- since you were little.
- So I made things...
like kimchi jjigae...
- and doenjang jjigae.
- Did you make them...
- since when you were little?
- Yes. I made acorn jelly soup.
- I fried Spanish mackerel.
- Right.
- Did you do that?
- Yes.
It was dramatic.
(The story behind the birth of the cooking genius...)
(with 38 years of experience)
(It's getting more exciting to see the dinner by the two chefs.)
You've been cooking for a really long time, then.
I haven't even been cooking for ten years yet.
(And the novice chef with 10 years of experience is cooking...)
It looks so good.
I'll add potatoes and all in a minute.
(It already looks absolutely insane.)
Gosh. It looks delicious.
- Vegetables will release water.
- They will.
- I'll add the rest of them.
- Yes.
(Let's add the rest of the vegetables.)
(She pats them down.)
Will we be able to finish it?
(It's a lot.)
- We should share it.
- We can share it.
Let's share it.
- I think it'll cook well.
- Yes.
(Wait for a while after adding a bunch of vegetables.)
(When she opens the lid again...)
Gosh. The vegetable broth was added.
(As it boils, the chicken absorbs the sauce deeply.)
Gosh. Why don't I taste it, then?
Avengers, assemble.
(Siblings' Avengers, assemble.)
- Pepper?
- We can add more pepper.
(How will the Avenger-level chicken stew taste?)
The taste of kimchi is strong, isn't it?
Gosh. It's good.
(Gosh. It's good.)
It has a tang like tom yum kung.
It's a pleasant tang from the ripened kimchi.
(Sealing it to cook it for the last time)
(Sang Hun is on the move...)
(to make the beef brisket and dried radish leaf soup.)
(Savouring)
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
The aroma of the dried radish leaves is great.
Our Korean food aficionados will love it.
(Adding the beef briskets into the insane broth)
(After adding lots of pink beef briskets, )
(the broth from leaves and the juice from the briskets...)
(are meld into rich flavours.)
It's so good.
(The chicken stew and the soup are coming soon.)
It's hot.
It's so hot.
(She finally stays away from the fire in the midsummer.)
(If it's hot for me...)
What about the rest of us? Let me check.
(Worried about the ones working in the heat, )
(she goes out the gates.)
Gosh. They're done already.
- They're done already.
- What?
(What is she talking about?)
They're done. Gosh.
(Sang Hun peeks out through the gate.)
(What?)
- There's a sea now.
- How could this be possible?
- Gosh.
- She was an art major indeed.
Gosh. I'm shocked by her talents.
(The two are going crazy about the distant mural.)
Do you want to go and see it?
(Since the cooking is almost over, )
- They are good with their hands.
- I know.
(let's go see the mural ourselves.)
When did they match the colours?
- I know.
- It's hard to do so.
Gosh. They'll finish it today.
Goodness. After finishing that, they'll add fish tomorrow.
Come on.
(The three are so into the mural they didn't hear them coming.)
You're truly amazing.
Are you done cooking?
- Cooking isn't a big deal.
- From a distance,
it looks incredible. Do you just need to paint fish?
The sketch is amazing.
- It's incredible.
- Really?
- I'm in shock.
- Yes.
(Yoon Seo looks at the mural while they compliment it.)
- Really?
Yes. Look how fast you did it.
Is it even possible?
Really? Does it look pretty from a distance?
- It looks magnificent.
- Gosh. It's really shocking.
I can't wait to see it from a distance too.
(It's high praise coming from Jung Ah, who's a hardcore thinker.)
Gosh. It'll look beautiful when they paint in the fish.
Gosh. The colours are great too.
We'll paint the fish and boats tomorrow, right?
You're so good at this.
- Are you done cooking already?
- Yes.
- It's simmering. We're all done.
- Really?
We just need to set the table.
Gosh. Yoon Seo is so cute. You're like a baby painter.
She is different because she learned the skills.
- Yes, of course.
- Right?
Gosh. Look how detailed You Seok is.
He's adding the whites and all.
Is it okay for You Seok to add white detail on his own?
I'm adding my artistic touch...
- to it.
- You're not an art major.
- I got the chief's permission.
- Really?
- Of course.
- Am I the chief?
(I've already discussed it with the art-major chief.)
I think he's mimicking the bubbles of the waves.
If you say it's mountains, it looks like mountains too.
Does it look like mountains? Hold on.
- I see. It's because of the green.
- I mean...
- They do look like mountains.
- If you think they are mountains...
Isn't it okay to call them mountains?
- You're right.
- The bottom layer is the sea.
The middle one can be the mountains while the top is the sky.
- Yes.
- It can be.
It's up to our interpretation, isn't it?
("Art is open to interpretation.")
When we add the fish and the boats tomorrow,
- it'll look like the sea.
- Totally.
(Sang Hun finds Yoon Seo adorable.)
- Let's hurry back.
- Yes, shall we?
(They leave as they have cooking to do.)
- It shouldn't be reduced too much.
- Right.
- Come back when you're done.
- Okay.
We're done.
Gosh. They've successfully painted...
so much in such a limited time.
(They're once again impressed by the younger ones' efforts.)
- It's truly amazing.
- Their backs are soaked with sweat.
They'll do fine. They'll finish it nicely.
Gosh. It feels much better now that the sun has set.
What colour is that?
(She goes straight to him with a roller...)
Use this one.
(and dips it without hesitation.)
Add the detail once I paint the background.
- Okay.
- Right under here.
I just need to paint the borders.
(Now, the three siblings are in perfect sync...)
(even without speaking a word.)
That's it. Good job, You Seok.
(In the wreckage)
(Left by the storm)
(Gentle waves roll on as if nothing ever happened)
(Flying creatures and swimming creatures)
(You've become paints)
(And now I'm a brush)
It's done.
(They've spent two hours at the same spot...)
(while painting again and again.)
(The empty gray wall has become a blue sea.)
- I'm so proud.
- Isn't it fun?
(The empty gray wall has become a blue sea.)
Painting is supposed to be very hard...
because you have to use your arm nonstop.
I'm so proud of myself.
I'm glad you are.
I know nothing about art.
Look at it from a distance, You Seok.
(Proud You Seok, and Sun Young and Yoon Seo can't leave the spot.)
- It looks pretty, though.
- I don't like it.
It's pretty.
I wanted to do better.
There's no problem. Let's do it tomorrow.
(What will be added to this painting tomorrow?)
Good job.
(Sun Young comes back with her head hung low.)
(Good job!)
Well done, painters.
Yoon Seo and I are not satisfied with it.
From a distance?
I'm so proud of it, but they aren't happy with it.
I'm a perfectionist.
(Laughing)
Only You Seok is proud of it.
I'm so proud of it. I'm happy.
Right? Look at it from here.
- We can see it from here.
- It looks amazing from here.
It's so pretty.
It's great when we see it from here.
It'll look different tomorrow when it's dried.
- Gosh. I'm exhausted.
- Well done. Really.
(For those who are exhausted...)
Should we set the table now?
We should get ready to set the table.
(Today's highly anticipated dish is finally ready.)
It's crazy. I can't wait to have it.
(It looks so good they have to try it now.)
(She quickly takes out the ripened kimchi first.)
Are we eating now?
- I'll get the scissors.
- Gosh. It looks good.
- The kimchi smells incredible.
- Gosh.
(Well-simmered ripened kimchi that smells crazy)
Gosh. It looks good.
- Be careful. It's hot, isn't it?
- It's okay.
(The two are blown away by the chicken stew.)
- Won't this be enough for us?
- Yes.
It's too much.
It smells really good.
(They'll only have this much...)
(of the well-seasoned chicken and potatoes.)
(Carefully carrying it as it's heavy)
Gosh. It's crazy.
Gosh. It looks really amazing.
It looks so good.
Gosh. It smells incredible.
(Surprised)
(Dropping)
(Charging...)
(toward the ripened kimchi chicken stew)
Jung Ah.
Goodness.
Gosh. My goodness.
It's dried radish leaf soup.
- What?
- Sang Hun made it.
(Here's also the cooking genius's...)
(beef brisket and dried radish leaf soup!)
- Gosh.
- It looks so delicious.
(Sun Young and Yoon Seo regain their energy...)
(as the table is getting full.)
It's like a snack we have in the middle of work.
(They forget about the mural before they knew it.)
My goodness.
(The siblings' first dinner in Yeosu for the younger siblings...)
(who worked so hard)
(Jung Ah's ripened kimchi chicken stew...)
(with tangy umami)
(Sang Hun's beef brisket and dried radish leaf soup...)
(with rich and aromatic flavours)
(They sit in the shade of the protected tree...)
(with the small port as a background.)
(They can't help but clap.)
Goodness. Our cooking genius.
I can't wait to try the soup Sang Hun made.
- It's dried radish leaf soup. Yes.
- Are these dried radish leaves?
- It's dried radish leaf soup.
- It looks like meat soup.
- It's made with meat.
(How does it taste?)
(Humming)
It tastes good.
(Eating a lot of radish leaves)
(How is it?)
- It tastes just like meat soup.
- Yes.
- I never had it before.
- Dried radish leaves are good.
Right.
(Dried radish leaves seasoned with beef brisket's savoury flavour)
Dried radish leaf soup?
(Gasping)
(Enlightened)
It's very deep and rich.
- I mean the broth.
- It's just like meat soup.
(The professional home cook tries a lot of chunks.)
Sang Hun, you're an amazing cook.
- Seriously.
- Dried radish leaves...
Your soup is delicious.
How is it spicy and refreshing?
What's in it?
He made the broth properly with anchovies.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Is that why the flavour is deep?
- It's so delicious.
He also added shiitake mushrooms.
(And a natural flavour from shiitake mushrooms)
- What's in it?
- It's so good.
I can never make this kind of flavour.
(A broth carefully simmered with the finest ingredients)
It's excellent.
(Now that they increased their appetite with broth, )
(it's time to start the real game.)
(This is irresistible.)
I can't wait for the drumsticks.
(The insane-looking ripened kimchi)
(Her eyes are fixed on it.)
(Her mouth is watering.)
(However...)
The pickled garlic is amazing.
- You Seok.
- Yes?
We were going to tear it by hand.
(I see...)
(Frozen)
- I thought...
- What are you...
- Put it down.
- He's cutting it horizontally.
What have you...
(The worst criminal)
We were going to tear it by hand.
(Joking)
- There's more kimchi.
- Just eat this.
- There's more.
- I was just kidding.
- I like to eat it like this.
- We were going to eat it like this.
- Me too.
- Doctor.
Don't people in the US eat it like this?
Thank you for the food.
(Sweat pouring down)
- It's chicken.
- Bon appetit.
I feel happy.
Thank you for the food.
My goodness.
- How is it?
- It's delicious.
(It's delicious with white rice.)
My goodness.
(White rice wrapped with ripened kimchi)
(If you're Korean)
- Here you go.
- Here's a chicken leg.
- It's good.
- Serve yourselves potatoes.
- We have more chicken.
- Gosh.
(It's coming.)
A chicken leg for You Seok.
Thank you.
(An explosion of umami flavour)
It's delicious.
(Electrifying)
For kimchi lovers, this is the ultimate treat.
That's me.
- Do you like kimchi?
- This kimchi is really amazing.
Even without many side dishes...
(Ripened kimchi makes you forget other side dishes.)
- Right.
- This is all you need.
Usually, when you eat...
(Nodding)
(Headbanging on the side)
This is so good.
(This is hip-hop.)
The ripened kimchi is insane.
(How about a chicken leg seasoned with ripened kimchi?)
(Humming in surprise)
It's so good.
(Tender chicken leg meat)
(Getting goosebumps)
(Picking up a perfectly seasoned drumstick)
(Eating)
(Humming)
Gosh, I got it all over myself.
(He goes for it without caring.)
(Shouting)
(Humming)
A chicken leg for You Seok.
(Finishing with ripened kimchi is a must.)
It's delicious.
(After a ripened kimchi wrap)
It's really good.
It's delicious.
(Tearing with both hands)
- The food is so good.
- Serve yourself more.
It's so good.
(She starts sucking on it.)
We have a lot of chicken.
(Relieved)
(A trace of bone-picking)
This type of kimchi is rare.
(Grabbing a big piece of meat)
What do we do with this kimchi?
(Right into her mouth)
It's really good. You should have some too.
- This kimchi is...
- It's insane.
(This time, it's chicken leg meat with ripened kimchi.)
(The perfect balance of crunch and tenderness)
(This is making me angry.)
- Jung Ah, it's so good.
- Right?
I don't need anything else.
(On the other hand)
Ripened kimchi is packed with probiotics.
(After taking a deep, reverent breath)
That is good...
Not with napa cabbage but with young radish...
The potatoes are really good.
Aren't they good?
Like this...
(Potatoes that have soaked up every bit of flavour)
You have to eat it with potatoes.
Are the potatoes that good?
(Bright red potatoes...)
(and a spoonful of white rice)
(Ready to be possessed by the divine)
Among everything I've had on this show,
this is one of the top.
It could be greasy because of the meat.
- That's completely removed.
- Right? Because of kimchi.
But it has a deep flavour.
(The ripened kimchi cuts through the richness and adds depth.)
You can still taste the meat's full aroma.
It's not just light. It has an incredible depth to it.
No amount of money can buy...
- kimchi like this.
- Right.
This kimchi is rare.
(Fantastic ripened kimchi that increased the chicken stew's flavour)
What do we do with this kimchi?
(I give it a round of applause.)
It's impossible to make it taste good only with kimchi.
You have to season it well.
- Jung Ah seasoned it perfectly.
- Right.
- Of course. I can't make this.
- You have to season it well.
This is the type of kimchi only elders can make.
You can't find it in Seoul.
It's impossible.
(Chef Yum's spicy and sweet seasoning is added.)
While you were painting...
(Sweet and spicy)
It got split.
There's depth in the kimchi's flavour.
The umami taste is insane.
(Moist chicken seasoned with the broth)
(Getting one more bite)
This is a tasty restaurant.
I came here after a long time.
(Extremely excited)
This is a tasty restaurant.
The food is so good.
(Their food is very good.)
When will we get to eat ripened kimchi chicken stew...
and dried radish leaf soup under this beautiful tree again?
You can't make this at home.
(The food genius who attained enlightenment)
Gosh.
(In his hand is...)
(a ladle.)
I tried the broth earlier.
(As expected, the goal is the broth.)
It was excellent.
Seriously.
(Soaking the grains of rice)
(Slurping in)
(This is life.)
Viewers.
- I wish we could eat together.
- It's a bummer.
It's truly a bummer.
- Where are you looking at?
- What?
Are you talking to the sky?
A camera is up there.
- The sky?
- Viewers, you must try this.
It's a sign of respect.
- We should always look up...
- Like this.
To our viewers.
I can't look down at them like this.
Viewers.
I'm talking to the highest camera.
- Viewers.
- Gaze up with reverence.
I should gaze up at them with reverence.
She's right.
(Laughing)
Will there be another day...
- when we work this much...
- And eat a lot.
And eat this much?
What time are we getting up tomorrow?
- Tell us now.
- Right.
Tomorrow, you'll split into two groups...
- Oh, my gosh.
- and work.
(As always, the labour game returns.)
(The professional labour participant is already dreading it..)
(The one who enjoys playing games is happy.)
(The most challenging)
(Work in the sea)
(It's relatively peaceful.)
(Work on land)
(Rope wrapped around the waist)
(Their fate hangs on one single rope.)
(What will be the result of the random draw?)
(The cooking battle returns.)
(But looking a little suspicious)
(Eccentric cooks are here.)
(And Princess Jung Ah as the judge)
(This time, the theme is pork.)
(In their hands, )
(a spectacular transformation of pork)
(Cooking Battle 2 by eccentric chefs is coming soon.)